<!-- NOTE: In order to work with Unity, this file must be encoded as ANSI or UTF-8 without BOM -->
<config>

	<!-- G E N E R A L -->
	<text>
		<id>paused</id>
		<eng>Simulation currently paused.</eng>
		<spa>Simulación que se encuentra en pausa.</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>submit</id>
		<eng>Submit</eng>
		<spa>Presentar</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>begin</id>
		<eng>Begin</eng>
		<spa>Comenzar</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>continue</id>
		<eng>Continue</eng>
		<spa>Continuar</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>ok</id>
		<eng>OK</eng>
		<spa>OK</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>next</id>
		<eng>Next</eng>
		<spa>Siguiente</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>prev</id>
		<eng>Back</eng>
		<spa>Anterior</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>tutorial</id>
		<eng>Tutorial</eng>
		<spa>SPA</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>guidelines</id>
		<eng>Guidelines</eng>
		<spa>SPA</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>progress</id>
		<eng>Progress</eng>
		<spa>Progreso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>loading</id>
		<eng>LOADING...</eng>
		<spa>CARGANDO...</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>paused</id>
		<eng>Paused</eng>
		<spa>Hizo una pausa</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>exit</id>
		<eng>Exit</eng>
		<spa>Salida</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>table</id>
		<eng>Table</eng>
		<spa>Tabla</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>cancel</id>
		<eng>Cancel</eng>
		<spa>Cancel</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>run</id>
		<eng>Run</eng>
		<spa>Ejecutar</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>confirmSubmit</id>
		<eng>Click Submit if you are satisfied with your answers or Cancel if you wish to change an answer before moving on.\n\nOnce you click Submit, you will not be able to change a previous answer.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>iguana</id>
		<eng>Iguana</eng>
		<spa>Iguana</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>iguanaHome</id>
		<eng>Iguana Home</eng>
		<spa>Casa Iguana</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>iguanaFacts</id>
		<eng>Iguana Facts</eng>
		<spa>Hechos Iguana</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>textareaPlaceholder</id>
		<eng>Type answer here.</eng>
		<spa>Por favor, escriba su respuesta.</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- T I M E O U T S -->
	<float>
		<id>calloutTime</id>
		<value>30</value>
	</float>
	<float>
		<id>timeoutTime</id>
		<value>60</value>
	</float>
	<text>
		<id>timeoutForwardButton</id>
		<eng>Click Next to continue.</eng>
		<spa>Haga clic Siguiente para continuar.</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>timeoutBegin</id>
		<eng>Click Begin to continue.</eng>
		<spa>Haga clic Comenzar para continuar.</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>timeoutSubmit</id>
		<eng>Please answer the question and click Submit to continue.</eng>
		<spa>Por favor responder a la pregunta y haga clic Enviar para continuar.</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>timeoutDisabledSubmit</id>
		<eng>Please answer the question.</eng>
		<spa>Por favor responder a la pregunta y haga clic en el botón Enviar para continuar.</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>timeoutRun</id>
		<eng>Please click Run.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>timeoutPlayPause</id>
		<eng>Please click Play.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- P E O P L E-->
	
	<!-- I N T R O -->
	<text>
		<id>heatLamp</id>
		<eng>Heat Lamp</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>metalMesh</id>
		<eng>Metal Mesh</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>linoleum</id>
		<eng>Vinyl</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide2</id>
		<eng>Your science class has a green iguana named Iggy.\n\nIggy lives in a very large home that is made of metal mesh. The home is in the science classroom.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide3</id>
		<eng>Some of your classmates have noticed problems with Iggy's behavior. He has a good home, but he could be happier!\n\nYour job is to learn about the problems and explore ways of solving them.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide4</id>
		<eng>Iggy's cage is on a table in a dark area of the classroom.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide5</id>
		<eng>The cage is made of metal mesh and the cage floor is made of vinyl.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide6</id>
		<eng>A heat lamp is at the top of the cage. The lamp is always on.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide7</id>
		<eng>Now look at Iggy's behavior in his home. Click Run to see his behavior over the course of a day.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide7b</id>
		<eng>When you have finished watching the video, click Next.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<text>
		<id>test1</id>
		<eng>You and your classmates do more research and conclude that Iggy is awake and active at night because even though the classroom is dark at night, the heat lamp gives off lots of light.\n\nOne of your classmates makes some suggestions to make Iggy's home darker .</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>test2</id>
		<eng>Let's turn off Iggy's heat lamp at night so it is dark in his cage.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>test3</id>
		<eng>Instead of the lamp we have in Iggy's cage now, let's use a special ceramic heat lamp that gives off heat but no light.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>testYes</id>
		<eng>Yes, this will work.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>testNo</id>
		<eng>No, this will not work.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>

	<!-- CARTOON -->
	<text>
		<id>cartoonScript</id>
		<eng>Green iguanas are among the largest lizards in the Americas, averaging around 6 feet and weighing about 20 pounds! They are challenging to care for because they are adapted for survival in their native habitat.\n\nThey live in warm, very humid rain forests in places like Central America. They need the moist air in the rain forests. They are adapted to get moisture mostly from the humid air, not by drinking.\n\nTo be active and digest their food, iguanas must lie still in very hot sun. They need high temperatures. Since they are adapted to get heat from the Sun above, they are not good at absorbing heat on the lower part of their bodies.\n\nThey spend their days in tree branches, moving from warmer areas... ...to cooler areas to keep their bodies at the right temperatures. Pet iguanas must be able to move from warmer to cooler areas in their cages.\n\nIguanas usually live near water and are excellent swimmers.\n\nThey are vegetarians; they eat only leaves, flowers, and fruit.\n\nIguanas are active during the day and sleep at night. This means they do best with light in their cages in the day and darkness at night.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide8</id>
		<eng>Before you solve Iggy's problems, you need to learn more about iguanas.\n\nWatch the short animation about iguanas. The film will give you information about iguanas to help you make changes to Iggy's home.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide9a</id>
		<eng>Review the iguana facts below that you learned from the animation.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide9b</id>
		<eng>Iguanas need very moist air and high temperatures.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide10</id>
		<eng>Iguanas control their body temperature by moving in and out of warmer and cooler areas.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide11</id>
		<eng>Iguanas are adapted to absorb heat from above.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide12</id>
		<eng>Iguanas need 12 hours of darkness at night and 12 hours of strong light in the day.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- ITEM ONE -->
	<text>
		<id>slide13</id>
		<eng>The iguana facts will help you solve the problems with Iggy's home. You will be able to view these facts at any time.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide14</id>
		<eng>Your classmates noticed two strange things about Iggy's behavior. Iggy's strange behavior means that there is probably something wrong with his home.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>problems</id>
		<eng>PROBLEMS</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide16</id>
		<eng>Iggy is always hanging on to his heat lamp! He does not want to be anywhere else.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide17</id>
		<eng>The classroom's Iggy Webcam shows that Iggy is awake and active at night.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide18a</id>
		<eng>Let's start by trying to solve problem 1.\n\nIggy is always hanging on to his heat lamp! He does not want to be anywhere else.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide18a.2</id>
		<eng>Based on the iguana facts, what is the most likely reason Iggy is hanging on to his heat lamp?</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide18b</id>
		<eng>Iggy likes being high up in his cage.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide18c</id>
		<eng>Iggy's home lacks moisture.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide18d</id>
		<eng>Iggy's home is too cold for him.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide18e</id>
		<eng>Iggy is not getting enough to eat.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide18f</id>
		<eng>Answer the question and click Submit.\nClick Iguana Facts to review facts about iguanas.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- ITEM TWO -->
	<text>
		<id>slide19</id>
		<eng>You and your classmates do some research and learn that Iggy is clinging to his heat lamp because his home is too cold.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide20a</id>
		<eng>Below are some changes that could be made to Iggy's cage.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide20b</id>
		<eng>Move Iggy's branch closer to his heat lamp.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide21</id>
		<eng>Add a stronger heat lamp to Iggy's cage.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide22</id>
		<eng>Add a large rock for Iggy to lie on.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide23</id>
		<eng>Put a blanket at the bottom of Iggy's cage.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide24a</id>
		<eng>Click the change on the left that would most likely help with the problem of Iggy's home being too cold. Look at the facts about iguanas to help with your decision.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide24b</id>
		<eng>Explain how this idea would solve the problem and why it would work better than the other options. Be sure to refer to any relevant Iguana Facts in your response.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide24c</id>
		<eng>Click one of the choices on the left and type your explanation. Click Iguana Facts to review facts about iguanas. When you are finished, click Submit.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- ITEM THREE -->
	<text>
		<id>slide25</id>
		<eng>Your classmates agree that the best idea is to add a more powerful heat lamp to Iggy's cage. This should make his cage warmer.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide26</id>
		<eng>Before you test to see if this is true, let's turn to problem 2. The classroom's Iggy Webcam shows that Iggy is awake and active at night. You have learned that iguanas need to sleep at night to be healthy.\n\nClick Next to continue.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	
	<text>
		<id>slide27</id>
		<eng>Based on your observation of Iggy's behavior, what fact about iguanas is related to Iggy's second problem (Iggy is awake and active at night) ?"</eng>		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide27OptionA</id>
		<eng>Iguanas need very moist air.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide27OptionB</id>
		<eng>Iguanas absorb heat from above.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide27OptionC</id>
		<eng>Iguanas need to move in and out of warmer and cooler areas.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide27OptionD</id>
		<eng>Iguanas need 12 hours of light and 12 hours of darkness.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide27Instructions</id>
		<eng>Answer the question and click Submit.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- ITEM FOUR -->
	<text>
		<id>slide28</id>
		<eng>You and your classmates do more research and conclude that Iggy is awake and active at night because even though the classroom is dark at night, the heat lamp gives off lots of light.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide29a</id>
		<eng>One of your classmates makes some suggestions to make Iggy's home darker.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide29b</id>
		<eng>Let's turn off Iggy's heat lamp at night so that it is dark in his cage.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide30</id>
		<eng>Instead of the lamp we have in Iggy's cage now, let's use a special ceramic heat lamp that gives off heat but no light.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide32</id>
		<eng>Using the Iguana Facts, evaluate each of the ideas. Choose whether or not the idea will work and explain why.
</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide32Instructions</id>
		<eng>Type your answers in the boxes on the left. Then click Submit.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- ITEM FIVE -->
	<text>
		<id>slide33a</id>
		<eng>One of your classmates sees a product that could help solve Iggy's problem with too much light at night. </eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33b</id>
		<eng>NEW! RepLife DAY-TO-NIGHT TIMER</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33c</id>
		<eng>The RepLife timer is a day-to-night dual timer device that provides complete 24-hour lighting cycles from dawn to nighttime. It has the following features.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33d</id>
		<eng>8 outlets</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33e</id>
		<eng>4 independently operated timer-controlled outlets</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33f</id>
		<eng>4 constant-power outlets</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33g</id>
		<eng>On/Off switch</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33h</id>
		<eng>2 timer dials</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide33i</id>
		<eng>3-foot heavy-duty power cord</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide34a</id>
		<eng>Another classmate brings in the special ceramic heat lamp.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide34b</id>
		<eng>RepLife 60-Watt Ceramic Infrared Heat Emitter</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide34c</id>
		<eng>Emits heat but no light for all types of reptiles!</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide35a</id>
		<eng>You and your classmates now have</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide35b</id>
		<eng>the RepLife timer;</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide35c</id>
		<eng>Iggy's heat lamp; and</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide35d</id>
		<eng>the RepLife ceramic heat lamp that gives off heat but no light.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide35e</id>
		<eng>Review the information about the RepLife timer and the RepLife ceramic heat lamp using the tabs on the left. Explain how to solve Iggy's sleeping problem with these materials. In your explanation, be specific about how each piece can be used to help solve the problem.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide35f</id>
		<eng>Review each approach by clicking the tabs on the left. Then type your answer and click Submit.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>tabTimer</id>
		<eng>Timer</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>tabCeramic</id>
		<eng>Ceramic Heat Lamp</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- ITEM SIX -->
	<text>
		<id>slide37</id>
		<eng>You and your classmates think that using both Iggy's heat lamp and the ceramic heat lamp with the RepLife timer can help to solve Iggy's sleeping problem.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide38a</id>
		<eng>Now, test whether the changes to Iggy's home have solved problems 1 and 2 (cold home and not sleeping at night). Click Run to see the results of</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide38b</id>
		<eng>using a new, stronger heat lamp; and</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide38c</id>
		<eng>using the new RepLife timer and ceramic heat lamp.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide39a</id>
		<eng>Iggy is now sleeping at night, but you and your classmates see that Iggy is still clinging to his heat lamp during the day.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide39b</id>
		<eng>This means the temperature is still not high enough for him in the daytime. The first problem is not solved!</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide40</id>
		<eng>Right now, Iggy's home is made entirely of metal mesh, except for the vinyl floor and wood frame.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide41</id>
		<eng>Your class decides to try replacing the metal mesh on the sides and back of Iggy's home with clear plastic panels. Doing this may keep more heat in the home. You call this design option 1.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide42</id>
		<eng>Now click Run to see how well option 1 works for Iggy.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide43a</id>
		<eng>Based on Iggy's behavior, does option 1 work to solve Iggy's cold home?</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide43OptionA</id>
		<eng>Yes, this will work.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide43OptionB</id>
		<eng>No, this will not work.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide43b</id>
		<eng>Explain your answer based on what you observed.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide43c</id>
		<eng>Answer the question and click Submit. You may click Run to observe Iggy's behavior again.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- ITEM SEVEN -->
	<text>
		<id>slide44a</id>
		<eng>One of your classmates is taking an engineering class. She is studying how air of different temperatures moves in our homes and other structures we build, such as greenhouses.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide44b</id>
		<eng>She shares a greenhouse simulation from class that she thinks is relevant to solving Iggy's problem. Click Run to view the animation.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide45a</id>
		<eng>Compare option 1 to your classmate's simulation.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide45b</id>
		<eng>Based on the simulation, explain why adding plastic sides does NOT make Iggy’s cage warm enough.  Be specific about the features of Iggy’s cage in relation to the simulation.
</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide45c</id>
		<eng>Review each approach by clicking the tabs on the left. Then type your answer and click Submit.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide45tabA</id>
		<eng>Greenhouse Simulation</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide45tabB</id>
		<eng>option 1</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide45tabC</id>
		<eng>option 2</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	
	<!-- ITEM EIGHT -->
	<text>
		<id>slide47</id>
		<eng>You and your classmates decide that replacing the top of the cage with plastic is probably the best way to retain warm air. This new plan (replacing the sides, back, AND top) is called option 2.</eng>
		<!-- Change by VarnerMiller 20120128, the new wording works better with the game mechanics
		<eng>You and your classmates agree that the best plan is one that covers the top, back and sides of Iggy's home with plastic, but leave the front open using metal mesh. You call this design option 2.</eng>
		-->
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide48</id>
		<eng>Click Run to see how well option 2 works for Iggy.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide49a</id>
		<eng>You and your classmates observe that option 2 works!</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide49b</id>
		<eng>Based on your observations, why does option 2 keep Iggy's home warmer than option 1 does?</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide49c</id>
		<eng>There is more plastic in option 1 than in option 2.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide49d</id>
		<eng>More cold air is trapped in Iggy's home in option 1 than in option 2.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide49e</id>
		<eng>Warm air is prevented from escaping out the top in option 2.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>	
	<text>
		<id>slide49f</id>
		<eng>More light is trapped in option 2 than is trapped in option 1.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide49g</id>
		<eng>Review each approach by clicking the tabs on the left. Then answer the question and click Submit.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>

	<!-- ITEM NINE -->
	<text>
		<id>slide52a</id>
		<eng>One of your classmates has done some research about iguanas and is worried that Iggy may get dehydrated, meaning his body will not get enough moisture.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide52b</id>
		<eng>Based on what you have learned in this task about iguanas, which of these two items is best at preventing Iggy from getting dehydrated?</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide52c</id>
		<eng>Another bowl of water in his new home</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide52d</id>
		<eng>An automatic water-misting system in his new home</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide52e</id>
		<eng>Explain why, referring to the iguana facts.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide52f</id>
		<eng>Answer the questions and click Submit.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide52g</id>
		<eng>Explain your answer.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide53</id>
		<eng>Take another look to see if you and your classmates have solved Iggy’s problems. Click Run to see.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	<!-- CONCLUSION -->
	<text>
		<id>slide55a</id>
		<eng>Thank you for your work.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	<text>
		<id>slide55b</id>
		<eng>Iggy is much more comfortable in his home now.</eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	
	
	<!--
	<text>
		<id></id>
		<eng></eng>
		<spa>Traducción en curso</spa>
	</text>
	-->
	
</config>